HEY!
We don't need your nagging in cover!
We're too poor, shy of superstardom No glossy photos, no billboard chart Sleeping on couches, playing basements Free minds won't bow to a corporate art They want us queen-shaven, posing pretty Selling our souls for a ten-year plan But we'd rather stink of cheap PBR Than sell our songs to a greased-up man
License our souls for a flashy tour, now we'll leave that ship at the dock.
Your velvet ropes and VIP rooms get fucked right up.
Still not famous, still not sorry, rather bleed truth than borrow their story.
O.A.N.R.
telling us what to play, we write our own rules and sing our own way.
Still not famous, still not sorry, we're all too proud for your sorry story You've been in a gorge, crank it till it bleeds, freedom's our drug, faith's just a disease
They promise exposure, a million streams But it's just state of mind in your teenage dreams We're fine with three fans in a sweaty room Trading our fame for creative perfume No neon signs, no corporate bailout We live for the core changes in our veins If the scene goes sideways, we'll still stay true Cause selling out's the only thing that's lame Contract for gold bars and grand illusions We laughed so hard we almost pissed
We're allergic to mansions and red guitar solos Give us scrappy, real, not famous, still not sorry Rather play truth than borrow their story No way in our telling us what to play We write our own rules and sing our own way Still not famous, still not sorry You loud, too proud for your sorry story He pitted a garage, crank it till it bleeds Freedom's our drug, fame's just a disease
No leather jackets in boardrooms No punched up smiles for ad campaign pains We'll stay broken, loud and restless While your stars decay and fames change
Still not famous, still not sorry Still not famous, still not sorry We'd rather bleed truth than bother story No way in our telling us what to play We write our own rules and sing our own ray Still not famous, still not sorry You loud, too proud for your sorry story Keep it in the garage, creak it till it bleeds Freedom's our drug, fame's just a disease
Here's to the unsold records and midnight scars!
Fuck your fame, we'll keep the scars!